[ Mac ]
How are we supposed to scale
back our energy costs...
when you are filling
this generator
with gasoline?
When did you start running
the bar on a gas
generator instead of--
About a week ago.
I've been doing it
for about a week.
Why would you do that?
Well, because, you know,
electricity's so expensive, man.
So I figured let's
get a generator and,
you know, run the bar on it.
Are you kidding me? Gasoline's,
like, a thousand times more
expensive than electricity.
And you know what, Charlie?
You shouldn't be making these
decisions anyway, okay?
You're not
the decision-making type.
[ Charlie ] Yeah.
As the brains of this
organization, I should've
made this decision.
Whoa, whoa. I'm sorry.
Since when did you
become the brains?
Uh, I'm sorry.
I've always been the brains.
What?
What are you talking about?
I thought I was the brains.
What the hell am I?
You're the looks.
Well, yeah.
Of course I'm the looks.
But I always thought
of myself as the brains
and the looks.
No, you're the looks.
I'm the brains.
Charlie's the wild card.
Whoa. That's awesome.
Yeah. Yeah, that's
the classic setup.
You know this, no?
Look, every great crew
in history has followed
that basic dynamic, right?
Looks, brains, wild card.
Think about it.
The A-Team did it.
Scooby-Doo did it.
The Ghostbusters did it.
Oh, shit.
Yes. Right?
Our problem
is that we don't stick
to that basic format,
and it gets us into trouble.
So what you're saying
is that by breaking
from that format,
we're actually limiting
our ability to be
as successful...
as those organizations.
You're totally right, dude.
Great.
On to the matter at hand.
We're getting plowed in the ass
by the oil companies
and the gas companies...
with their 10-gallon hats
and their rotten,
ass-plowing hearts.
So, as the brains
of this organization,
I came up with a plan.
Lay it on us, bud.
It involves pulling up our
bootstraps,
oiling up a couple of asses,
and doing a little plowing
of our own.
Mmm.
Pow!
Not gay sex.
Okay. 'Cause that's
what it sounded like.
Okay, okay, okay.
What did you mean?
We're gonna solve
the gas crisis.
♪
♪♪
Charlie, the plan
is simple, okay?
Is it?
Yes.
We go to a bank.
We talk to a loan officer.
We get a hefty loan to buy
a bunch of gasoline.
Mm-hmm.
We take that gasoline.
We store it in the basement.
We wait a few months.
When the gas prices
skyrocket, we sell it,
make a huge profit.
Yeah, man.
If the guy doesn't seem
like he's going for it,
I'll show him this
big-breasted-women chart.
[ Charlie ] Mm-hmm.
And that'll win him over.
Yeah, I'm sure it will,
'cause that's great,
and the plan's
actually pretty great.
The problem I'm having
with it is that I don't
have anything to do.
No. You do have
something to do.
You're the wild card.
You sit there looking crazy
and capable of anything.
Yeah.
Ohh. That's--
Yeah, you set the tone
for the whole meeting.
Okay.
So if I'm, like, there
while you guys are talking,
and I'm just, like, uh--
That's terrible.
That was my--
That was my wild card face.
What message are you
trying to send with that?
Was it not a good one?
Well, so what if it's
more like-- like, I'm, um--
You want '''em to think
you're gonna take a dump, or--
That's what that looks like?
I don't know what
message you were trying--
Oh, man.
You're forcing it.
Oh, my God.
Yeah, you're
forcing it.
I better look in a mirror,
'cause I don't know what I'm
doing, and what it looks like
feel like two different things.
I'm gonna supervise, 'cause
there's no way he should
be making this decision.
Walk me through it, dude,
'cause I just don't see it.
I'm gonna draw another woman.
It's not a rape van.
It's a spy van.
It looks like a rape van to me.
But whatever.
Dennis, you gotta
look at this.
What is this?
Bruce Mathis is about to
give away all of Mom's money.
What are you talking about?
In two days, some Muslim
cultural center...
is about to get
a giant check made
out of our cash.
- And we gotta get that back.
- Listen. This jamoke is giving
our money to terrorists.
And we gotta prove it.
Um, Dee, Mom gave all of our
money to Bruce. You were never
gonna get it anyway.
Oh, no, no, no.
I was. See, I had a plan.
I was gonna eliminate
everybody else and be
the only surviving heir.
So... help.
Uh, so when you say "eliminate,"
you mean you were gonna kill me?
Uh, I don't know.
No. Yes.
Maybe I was going to.
Maybe I wasn't.
The point is moot now.
Can you please help me out here?
So you were planning
on killing me?
You're still
talking about that?
Listen, listen. Stop arguing.
Are you gonna help us or not?
We got no time here.
Pass.
Pass?
Yeah, pass. Super pass.
UÜÜber pass.
How do you super pass
on something like this?
We gotta get that money.
I pass!
Because you were
planning on killing me.
I feel like you're really
focused on one tiny part of
what I'm trying to talk about.
It's a very big part of your--
It's just a couple of words.
Just go away.
I'm trying to draw breasts.
Focus on the words "money"--
and pretty women.
and "Bruce,"
and "me," and "help."
All right. And what
is the reason you're
requesting a loan today?
Wait for it.
Gasoline.
- Excuse me?
- Don't rush me.
Don't rush him.
Thank you. I feel rushed.
Look. Here's the plan.
You give us a shitload of money.
We buy a shitload of gasoline.
We wait 12 months.
We sell the gasoline.
And make a shitload
of profit.
Gentlemen, we tend to give loans
to businesses, not, um--
She's not getting it.
Get the graph.
Oh, yeah. The graph.
We have a graph.
Yeah. Check this out.
Now these are
the gas prices last year.
These are the gas prices
this year.
And this is what
the gas prices will be.
- And what are those?
- Uh, these are gorgeous women
with heaving breasts.
Why?
Uh, well, to be perfectly
honest, we sort of thought...
we'd be speaking
to a man today, so--
Yeah.
Is there any way
that we could
talk to your boss?
- Because I think he would
understand more better.
- My boss is a woman.
Really?
Your boss is a woman?
Now, this is a strange bank.
Okay. Well, I am definitely
rejecting your request...
for $300,000
to buy gasoline.
Dennis, you're on.
Yeah.
You know, I just had
a crazy thought.
How's about I take you
in the back and--
Oh.
"change your mind"?
Or how about we all go
in the back and have great sex?
- What are you doing?
- Hmm? I'm playing
the wild card here, man, so--
No, dude.
Just let Dennis
do his thing, okay?
I can be very sensual
with a woman, all right?
You will enjoy it.
Now is not the right time
to pull the wild card, okay?
Let me do my thing.
Let me do the seducing.
Look, let Dennis bang her
so we can get our loan.
Here's a scenario.
What if she wanted to bang me,
or you for that matter--
You can't pull the wild card
when I have my shirt off.
That should be a rule.
Yes, that's a rule.
Well, your shirt's not off.
Well, now it is,
goddamn it, bitch.
Oh, yeah?
Back off.
Oh, wow, now, baby.
Come on, man.
This is my job.
Now I feel like
I should do it.
What are you doing?
Huh?
Goddamn it.
Well, okay, so--
Why don't you decide?
Which one of us do you want
to take you in the back
and bang you?
My intel tells me
that Bruce moved into
this crappy apartment complex.
Where did you get
your intel?
I waterboarded some guy.
Told me everything.
You tortured somebody?
Oh, yeah. Big time.
- What do you see?
- I can't see shit.
Why would you tint
the inside of the windows?
I don't want anybody
to see in.
We can't see out, Frank.
I might've overdone it
a little bit.
You think so?
Whoa, whoa. That's Bruce.
- This guy?
- That's the guy walking there.
- Start the car.
- Are you sure that's him?
[ Frank ]
Let's follow him.
I'm gonna take some pictures.
[ Groans ]
I got it working.
Let's go.
All right, there's--
The gas pedal is stuck.
Well, wobble it.
Wobble it?
Yeah, wobble it back and forth.
Wiggle it. Wiggle it.
All right.
[ Engine Starts ]
That's it. That's it.
Now hit it. Whoa!
Aaah! Oh, God.
What are you trying to do?
You're giving me whiplash.
You're blinding me.
Calm down for a second.
Hold on.
Oh, man.
Son of a bitch.
Will you stop with
that for one second?
Hey, assholes.
[ Shutter Clicking ]
Hey, what the hell
was that about?
I can't believe Dee keeps her
life savings in her sock drawer.
That's a dumb place to hide it.
She's an investor now.
She'll thank us later.
You know what, guys?
I'm sorry. Can I--
I gotta bring something up.
Can I bring something up?
Because if I don't, it's
gonna stew up inside me.
It's gonna
drive me crazy.
What's up, man?
I kinda can't believe
that you guys took your
shirts off back there, man.
I mean, I feel like
you really sold me
down the river.
The Ghostbusters
would never do something
like that to each other.
I can't believe
you guys did it.
What are you doing?
- No trash cans. Only cars.
- Whoa. Cool your jets, guy.
We paid for this gas.
It's gonna be a while, so--
[ Whistles ]
Stop now. You can't do this.
What? Come on, man.
Only cars.
Ah, geez. All right.
Well, wild card,
do your thing.
So help me, God,
I'll blow this place
to kingdom come, guy.
Not that. Not that.
Jesus Christ, Charlie.
Come on, man.
No. We just gotta figure out
a way...
to get this gas
back to the bar
without using the barrels.
Well, how the hell
are we gonna do that?
Aaah!
[ Coughing ]
All right, barrel number six
is done, dudes.
Mac, this doesn't seem
to be the best--
This is not working, okay?
We are actually
losing money driving
back and forth...
from that gas station
all day long.
You burn up your product--
Plus, I have swallowed
a good deal of it,
and it's a damn waste.
That's not good.
Yeah, and gas has gone up
seven cents since this morning.
He puts a new thing on the sign
every time we pull in there.
We're screwing
ourselves here, guys.
Hold on. Let's not freak out.
Let's not freak out.
The plan is not
working though, man.
We just need to adjust our
business model to meet the needs
of a changing marketplace.
That's all.
That's money talk.
Let's talk money.
We gotta make some money
in the short term.
Well, how the hell
are we gonna do that?
I got a plan.
We'd like to return
some gas, please.
- Yeah. Don't worry, bro.
Got receipts.
- I can't do that.
You can't do it,
or you won't do it?
Both.
Not yet, buddy.
Okay, bro.
You want to play
hard ball, fine.
You're about to
experience the hard knocks
of a free market, bitch.
Get ready to feel it
where it hurts.
Your dick.
No. No, not his dick.
His-- His wallet.
Yup.
Your wallet.
- Here we are. This is it.
- Are you sure
this is his place?
Yes. Yes, yes.
My intel says so.
Okay, listen.
Take these box cutters.
Put 'em in his bedroom.
Take this fertilizer.
Toss it in the closet.
What the hell
are we doing that for?
'Cause when I call the cops
on him, they'll come and find
all this bomb-making shit,
and they'll arrest
his money-stealing ass.
We don't want
to call the cops.
They'll find the bug
I'm gonna plant.
That's a baby monitor, Frank.
You're planting a baby monitor?
Yeah. A lot of people
are bugging their babies
these days.
I guess babies
can't be trusted.
What exactly is it you're
expecting to find here?
A lot of shady shit.
Like what?
Like maybe Bruce
is banging dudes.
Why would that be shady?
Maybe the dudes are babies.
What?
Bruce is not banging
any baby dudes.
Look, we're going back
to the original plan, okay?
We're gonna put the frame
on him, we're gonna be heroes
among the community,
and I'm gonna get all of my
money back as a reward.
All my money.
Well, whatever.
It was probably gonna
end up mine eventually, so--
Okay. There's something
I want to talk to you about.
Were you planning on offing me,
and then offing Dennis also?
Frank, we are in
the middle of something.
I don't have time to chitchat
with you about stuff right now.
Were you planning on offing me?
I didn't say that.
You didn't deny it either.
Uh, deny it?
Do I have to deny
something so crazy?
Give me the baby monitor.
I'll hide it for you.
Capitalism at work.
This oughta show
the son of a bitch.
All right, buddy,
now explain to me
how exactly...
we're gonna
calculate the totals.
Oh, it's easy, dude.
You pour gas into
the car using one of
these funnels, right?
And I count how much gas
is going into the car.
All right, let me--
Let me just stop you
right there.
How exactly are you planning
on counting a liquid?
Uh, I know how
to count, dude.
I'm not--
Okay, you do it.
You do it, Mac.
Because I can't speak to him.
Well, say free market 101--
You gotta have customers to
have a working business, right?
So we gotta attract attention.
I for one suggest me blowing
fireballs to get that attention.
Fireball-- Where is that
coming from? No.
We're not blowing fireballs
around 10 containers of--
People will see it
from the street.
We have 10 containers
of gasoline.
The lighter, please.
What the hell are you--
Thank you, sir.
Let me please reiterate--
He understands.
my strong opposition--
Trust me, Dennis.
I know what I'm doing.
to this idea.
This is really unsafe, dude.
Do not blow that fireball.
Whoa!
Wow. Okay, wow.
I take back everything
I just said. That was amazing.
Oh, dude.
I'm doing
one of those, baby.
I can do it bigger.
You can do it bigger?
No, Charlie.
Let me do it.
Make sure it's bigger.
If you're gonna do it,
make sure you-- Wait.
Aaah!
Whoa.
Oh, goddamn it.
Whoo!
You burned my head.
[ Laughing ]
Oh, I think I burned him.
Really?
Ow! Ow! Jesus Christ.
Easy, camper. Easy, camper.
Relax.
You're gonna feel better.
How can I relax?
Just stop. Just stop.
Okay.
Do you have anything
other than a towel
and duct tape?
Not really.
New plan.
We're going to a hospital.
Oh, whoa. Actually, bro,
you know what?
I think we're gonna
be done with your plans
for a little while.
Because the system you set up--
It ain't working.
So I got a new system.
Me-- Both the brains
and the looks.
Charlie, you're still gonna be
the wild card, 'cause that
fireball you blew was badass.
It was great, right?
You just kinda got in the way.
Yeah.
Mac, check this out though.
You're gonna be the muscle.
No. I--
I think we gotta stick to
the paradigm that we've set up--
The A-Team, Scooby-Doo--
No, no, no.
Your "paragon"
is failing us, man.
It's a "paradigm," but yeah.
- It wasn't working.
- It's not working.
What happened was we
confused your bossiness
with braininess,
and those two are
very different things.
Mm-hmm.
That is what happened.
So check it out
though, man.
I got a new plan.
This is what we're gonna do.
Yeah.
Yeah. We're gonna steal
Frank's rape van--
Mm-hmm.
because driving around with
all that gasoline is ruining
the interior of my car.
And I just--
I won't have it.
No.
Then we're gonna take
that van and we're
gonna offer people...
something that gas stations
just can't offer 'em.
What?
Gasoline directly
to their doorsteps.
Door-to-door gasoline
salesmen.
Oh, my God. That's amazing.
That's a brilliant
plan, right?
Brains, looks, brains.
Whatever, fine.
Then I'll be the muscle.
I'll muscle these pricks
into buying the gas and--
Ooh.
Actually, why don't you muscle
your way back by the van because
you look like a burned-up freak.
You know what?
A look is gonna be
a big part of this.
- I'm gonna get some disguises.
- Why would we need
disguises, Charlie?
So people don't know
who we are, you know?
- They already don't know.
- You're not letting
the wild card do his thing.
- Is there any reason
behind what you're doing?
- Wild card.
[ Man On TV ]
Stewart's up on his second shot
on the fairway.
Hole 15.
I'd say it's about 195 yards.
He has a seven iron.
[ Sharp Smack ]
I mean, how has he been
sitting there watching golf
for three hours?
I don't know. I don't know.
[ Man ]
Is that a baby monitor?
Oh! Shit. Cut it off.
Goddamn it.
Now he's suspicious of us.
Oh, no.
You are such a bad hider.
I'm a bad hider?
You never could hide.
It was hard to--
I bet you still hide your money
in your sock drawer.
[ Scoffs ]
My sock drawer?
Yeah.
Come on.
That would be stupid.
Yeah, you do.
You're lying to me.
Just shut up.
I'm not lying to you.
I'm getting outta here.
This is a setup.
Will you relax?
You're setting me up,
and I'm getting the hell out.
Frank, get back here.
You're not gonna
do this to me, girl.
I understand
what's goin' on.
Come back, Frank. Goddamn it.
- Okay, they're on the move.
- I know what's going on.
You think I was
born yesterday?
Hey, you son of a bitch.
Okay, go. Go, Mac. Go. Go.
[ Dee ]
What are you talking about?
Don't lie to me. I have my ways
of finding out things.
You'll be sor--
Oh, my God.
Is that a Muslim guy?
He's getting in my van.
[ Tires Squealing ]
- Oh, shit!
- [ Groans ]
[ Car Alarm Blaring ]
- Man, what--
Dude, seriously?
- Hey.
No. No. No.
[ Dennis ]
All right, well, just let me
do the talking, okay?
You gotta at least talk
with a Southern accent.
I'm not gonna talk
in a Southern accent.
It's bad enough
that you wore
this stupid disguise.
But we're oilmen.
We would have Southern accents.
- We don't need bolo ties
and stupid hats.
- Yes, we do. She's gonna--
Hello, ma'am.
Oh, what a lovely house dress.
[ Exaggerated Southern Accent ]
Yeah.
Well, you're looking
all sorts of good.
Now, you seem like...
a sweet, sophisticated,
nice, busy, young lady,
so we're not gonna
waste your time today.
Nah.
We're just a couple oilmen
in from Dallas,
and, well, we're itching
like a hound to give you
something you want.
What my--
[ Clears Throat ]
associate is trying to say...
is that we're here
to offer your community
a much-needed service--
Hells, yeah.
We want to fill you up,
if'n you are so inclined
as to let us.
Please let me
do the talking.
I got it.
Please let me--
Now we ain't gonna take no
for an answer now, you hear?
Okay? So don't be making me
sic my associate on you
here, all right?
[ Laughs ]
He don't take kindly to "no."
So can I fill you up or what?
Yeah.
You'd best get to stepping
because Johnny Law's a-coming.
Yeah. You might want to
start driving because she
called the cops on us.
Why is he talking like that?
Well, wild card over here
decided to lose his mind.
I say, I say, that's
just damn preposterous, boy.
Well, now
you're just talking
like Foghorn Leghorn.
All right, guys, I think it's
time we cut our losses and go
back to the original plan.
- Ah, the generator.
- No, not the generator.
Storing the gas in Paddy's.
All right.
It's too soon to
sell this gas anyway.
Just shut the door.
Go, go, go, go.
Okay, okay, okay.
[ Tires Squealing ]
All right, admit it.
That Muslim guy
was gonna rub me out.
And that's when you jumped out
of the van after I got out.
Admit it. Come on.
[ Gasps ]
Oh, my God.
I don't know what
you're talking about.
Oh, don't lie to me.
No! Okay!
Admit it!
Okay! Okay, I admit it.
What do you admit?
I admit anything
you want to hear.
Now you admit that Bruce Mathis
is a terrorist?
He's a terrorist.
And that you
are working for him.
Yes. I work for him.
We get our information
from the top.
The top cave.
Don't bullshit me.
That's all I got to say.
Oh, hey.
I like what
I'm seeing here, Frank.
Bring me up to speed.
I'm waterboarding your sister
because she's escalating
the plot to kill us.
- Dennis, help me.
- Why the hell
would I help you, Dee?
- You're still plotting
to kill me?
- No. Help!
Shut up. Shut up.
Shut up.
Yeah, shut up.
Tell me what's going on.
Hey, Frank, by the way,
we borrowed that pathetic
rape van of yours.
You gotta get that
gas pedal fixed, man.
[ Gasping ]
Mac rammed into some dude's
car, like, five
times.
It was amazing.
You guys took the van?
I thought
it was some Muslim guy.
No, not really.
Whoa! What is
going on in here?
Well, Frank's waterboarding Dee.
You guys? You took the van?
Well, hell, yeah.
Oh, my God.
I just realized something.
Frank is the muscle.
What?
The reason that
shit hasn't been
working out for us...
is because we are not
working with our full crew.
I'm the brains, you're the
looks, Charlie's the wild card
and Frank is the muscle.
Well, what's Dee?
She's the useless chick.
Ahh!Ahh!
Yeah.
Yeah.Yeah.
You see? We complete it.
We all complete the team.
Now if we stick together, guys,
we can do anything.
Now-- question.
Frank, does that waterboard
really work?
[ Laughs ]
You bet your ass.
I got Dee to admit
to things she never did.
Well, then it works.
Ha, ha! All right.
Then, gentlemen,
I got a new plan.
♪♪ [ Ghostbusters Theme ]
[ Tires Squeal ]
Okay, now, once we get
to Bruce's, we slip in
and we grab him.
Shouldn't you guys have
gotten these barrels out
of the van before we got in?
They're really heavy, Dee.
We've already had to do it,
like, a million times.
Where did you
get the money
for this gas?
Dee, will you shut up
and let me continue?
Frank, when we
get to the bar, you
waterboard the shit...
- out of Bruce
and get a confession.
- No problem.
Now, Dennis, you take that
confession to the police,
use your charm
and good looks, and
get that reward money.
Done and done.
Okay. Dee, you continue
to be useless.
Charlie and I will use that
reward money to pay off
our electricity bill.
Then we'll probably buy some
more gasoline because I feel
like that's a great plan.
- [ Pumping ]
- Wait.
Brakes don't--
Brakes don't work.
The gas pedal--
- No. I'm saying--
No. The brakes--
- Wiggle the gas pedal.
- Guys, why aren't
the brakes working?
- Because I cut the brakes.
Wild card, bitches!
Yee-haw.
What?
Holy shit.
- Oh, God.
- Oh, my God.
Jesus Christ, guys.
I can't stop this van.
Seriously?
Abort.
Abort. Abort!
Go!
[ Man On TV ]
Mastersfield steps up
to the tee,
eight strokes behind
the leader.
Hole number 17,
338 yards, dogleg left--
[ Explosion ]
Aaah!
[ Groaning ]
[ Car Alarms Blaring ]
[ Car Alarms Continue ]
Oh, goddamn it.
What the hell, man?
[ Frank ]
Aw, my van.
Why is someone
trying to ruin my life?
I didn't do anything
to anybody, man.
I love that car.
That, uh--
I love that car, man.
That's not Bruce, is it?
- Nope.
- [ Moaning ]
[ Man ]
♪ When there's
something strange ♪
♪ In your neighborhood ♪
♪ Who you gonna call ♪
♪ Ghostbusters ♪
♪ If there's something weird ♪
♪ And it don't look good ♪
♪ Who you gonna call ♪
♪ Ghostbusters ♪♪
♪♪ [ Synthesizer Plays ]
I ain't 'fraid
of no ghost.
[ Voices Speaking Backwards ]